你们认为怎样
Huh? So, what do you think?
乔伊的家
Casa de Joey.
我亲自装潢的
Huh? I decorated it myself.
少来了
Get out. No.
乔伊  这真是…
Wow, Joey, this is, uh...
艺术  是艺术没错
Art.  Art it is.
看看这个  这是咖啡桌吗
Well, check this out. Is it a coffee table?
下头是只美洲豹吗  根本就不用决定
Is it, uh, a panther? There's no need to decide.
好棒的抱枕
Hey, nice pillow.
请告诉我  这是真的布偶皮吗
So tell me, is this genuine Muppet skin?
这个会有水流动的东西太好了
Hey, excellent water-table thing.
谢谢  我也喜欢  但你知道吗
Thanks. I love this. But you know what?
这东西会让我想尿尿
It makes me want to pee.
对  我也会  我想这就是挑战所在
Yeah, me too. I think that's the challenge. Heh.
钱德怎么没来呢
Hey, how come, uh, Chandler didn't come?
那是因为他有事…
Well, uh, it's because he had a thing with the...
就是事
With the thing.
对  我懂了
Right. I got it.
再带我们去看看你家的其他部分吧
Why don't you show us the rest of your casa?
好
Yeah.
最好的一处  来吧
Uh, oh, oh, the best part. Come on.
恩
Huh?
嘿
Hey.
好棒的马桶
Nice toilet.
不是啦  是它的后面
No, no, no. Behind it.
你厕所也有装电话  没错
You have a phone in here? That's right.
我厕所也有…
I have a phone.
装电话
In here.
乔伊  你答应我一件事  什么
Joey, promise me something. Yeah.
别用这电话打给我
Never call me from that phone.
《老友记》 第二季 第17集: 艾迪的新家
Friends S02E17: The One Where Eddie Moves In
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
好了  来了
Okay, here we go.
抱歉  苹果派卖完了  最后一块被人买走了
Sorry, they were all out of apple pie. Someone just got the last piece.
（制片：塔德·史帝文斯）
老天  你们不会相信的
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. You are not gonna believe this.
我被发掘了
I have just been discovered.
等一下  四年前我就以法国之名  将你据为己有
Wait a minute. I claimed you in the name of France four years ago.
总之…
Anyway.
（制片：贝西·伯恩斯）
你们要答应我不要疯掉  也不要说有多棒   直到我说完
Promise you won't freak out and say how great this is until I'm done.
（编剧：亚当·却斯）
好  好
Okay. Okay.
我刚认识了一位  小唱片公司的制作人…
Uh, I just met this producer of this teeny record company...
她说我有一副  清新  与众不同的嗓音…
...who said, ahem, that I have a very fresh, offbeat sound...
她想请我录《臭猫》的试唱带
...and she wants to do a demo of "Smelly Cat."
我刚说过别这样了
Okay, I told you not to do that yet. Ha, ha.
好
Okay.
她还要拍音乐录影带
And she wants to do a video.
（导演：麦可·连贝克）
我还没讲完  好吗
I'm not done yet, okay? Ha, ha.
天啊
God. Okay.
如果一切顺利  他们还可能出一张专辑
If that goes well, they may even want to make an album.
我讲完了  那太棒了
I'm done now. Oh,that's great.
难以置信哦
That's unbelievable. Oh
罗斯  如果你爱我  那你就把派  从那人的的风帽上拿起来
Oh, God, Ross, if you care about me, get the pie out of the man's hood.
拿什么  他的风帽上有块派
Get the what? There's a pie in the hood. Go.
你在干嘛  抱歉  我的派掉进你的风帽里了
What are you doing?  I'm sorry. My pie was in your hood.
现在我得从那家伙的裤裆里把咖啡弄出来…
I have to get the coffee out of that guy's pants...
然后我七点前要赶回医院去
...and I'll be back in the hospital by 7.
可恶  罗斯  快滚出厕所
Damn it, Ross. Get your butt out of the bathroom.
别紧张  我在吹头发
Calm down. I'm blow-drying.
吹什么头发  你根本没有头发
Blow-drying what? You have no hair.
怎么回事
What's going on?
你男友在里头待了超过一小时
Uh, your boyfriend has been in there for an hour.
真不敢相信  这就好像我又跟他住在一起
It's like I'm living with him again.
我要睡觉时他在这里  醒来时也在  我要洗澡时他也在
He's here when I go to sleep, when I wake up, when I wanna shower.
我感觉好像又回到十六岁
Uh, I feel like I'm 16 again.
你已经不是十六岁了  而且你们两个又都是成年人了
Well, you're not 16. You're both adults now.
快出来  蠢货
Get out, you doofus!
其实  你们半斤八两
Or, you know, he's rubber and you're glue.
都是你的了
All yours.
你最好有把排水孔上的毛发清干净
I hope you cleaned your hair out of the drain.
闭嘴  闭嘴
Shut up.  Shut up.
别这样
Cut it out.
你以后别再这样了
I've never wanted you more.
你们怎么说  我该不该打电话给他
So, what do you say, boys? Should I call him?
人家就是这样说的
You know what they say:
〝问你拖鞋一个问题…
Ask your slippers a question...
你一定是疯了〞
...you're going crazy.
你好  嘿
Hello? Hey.
嘿
Hey.
抱歉  我今天没过去
Listen, I'm sorry I didn't make it over there today.
没关系
Oh, that's okay.
因为你有事嘛
You, uh... You had a thing.
我听说你那里很棒
Yeah, well, I hear the place looks great.
别提了  我愉快得很
Oh, forget about it. I'm having a ball, ha.
我们的公寓情况如何
How's the apartment doing?
很棒  只是普通的空间…
Oh, hey, it's terrific. I mean, it's a regular space...
…聚合地
...fest.
那就好
Oh, well, great.
我只是
Yeah, I just...
想打个电话打声招呼
...wanted to call and say hey.
好
Well, okay, then.
那是烤箱计时器的声音吗
Was that the oven timer?
没错  好朋友
That's right, my friend.
现在是看…  《海滩游侠》的时候了
It's time for Baywatch!  Baywatch!
噢
Oh.
你能相信他们居然让史黛芬妮得了皮肤癌吗
Can you believe they gave Stephanie skin cancer?
我真不敢相信他们升她为小队长
I can't believe they promoted her to lieutenant.
你会这么说是因为你爱上雅丝敏布莉
You're saying that because you love Yasmine Bleeth.
怎么可能有人不爱雅丝敏布莉
How could anyone not love Yasmine Bleeth?
嘿  在跑步了
Hey. Hey, they're running.
这正是全片的精华所在
See, this is the brilliance of the show.
他们应该继续跑下去
I say always keep them running.
从头跑到尾
All the time running.
跑吧
Run.
跑啊  雅丝敏  像阵风快跑
Run, Yasmine. Run like the wind.
但之前你说想一个人住的
But you wanted to live by yourself.
是啊  我还以为那样会很好
I did. I thought it'd be great.
我以为那样一来  我就有时间好好思考
I figured I'd have time alone with my thoughts.
但结果我发现  我根本没有你认为的那么多好思考的
But it turns out I don't have as many thoughts as you'd think.
那你何不找钱德商量  然后搬回去好了
Joey, why don't you talk to Chandler about moving back?
你们真的认为他会收容我吗
You really think he'd take me?
昨晚我们聊得很好…
We had a good talk last night...
但是当初我搬出去时  我伤他很深
...but when I moved out, I hurt him bad.
我保证  他一定会欢迎你搬回去的
I promise you, he would definitely want you back.
他才不会搬回来
I'm telling you, there's no way he's moving back.
但我们昨晚真的聊得非常愉快
But we had one of the greatest talks we ever had last night. Heh.
那就好像…
I mean, it was...
我们当初刚搬在一起住时一样
It was like when we first started living together.
我知道你不想听…
Look, I know you don't want to hear this right now...
但我们看到他在新家的样子  他真的很快乐
...but we've seen him in his new place. And he's happy.
他真的装潢过了
He's decorated.
钱德  他已经向前迈出去  好吗  你也不要眷恋过去
Look, Chandler, he has moved on, okay? You have to, too.
你要接受现在你们只是朋友的事实
No, you're just gonna have to accept the fact that you're just friends now.
你们不再是…
You're not...
室友了
...roommates anymore.
好了  菲比  准备好了吗
Okay, Phoebe. Ready to try one?
好
Okay. Ahem.
臭猫  臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
他们都喂你吃什么
What are they feeding you?
臭猫  臭猫
Smelly, smelly, smelly
真的很臭的臭猫
Really bad smelling smelly cat
哇  天啊
Oh, whoa! Oh, my God!
刚那是谁啊
I mean, like, who was that?
她们是你的合音天使  就在你的后面  亲爱的
They're your backup singers. Behind you, hon.
噢
Oh.
我以为她们只是来参观的
Oh, I thought they were just watching me.
就像是在看水族馆一样  好
Like at an aquarium, you know?  All right.
从头开始  好
From the top.  Okay. Ahem.
臭猫  臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
他们都喂你吃什么
What are they feeding you?
臭臭  臭臭
Smelly, smelly, smelly
非常臭  臭猫
Really bad smelling smelly cat
这不是你的错
It's not your fault
好了  抱歉
Okay, sorry.
我没感觉到…
I'm just not getting...
…大家都懂…
...that everyone, um, gets...
…这只猫到底有多臭
...how smelly this cat actually is.
或许我们可以聊一下这个
Maybe if we could talk about this...
因为我想要感觉到你们真的在乎这只猫
...because I need to feel that you really care about the cat.
这我们可以谈
Honey, we can talk about this.
只不过这里一分钟的租金要一百块美金
It's just that it's costing about $100 a minute to be in here.
好吧  那只猫是很臭  不过你们还是爱他  我们开始
Oh, okay. So, um, the cat stinks, but you love it. Let's go.
不  他不可能是迅猛龙
No, there is no way he was a velociraptor.
看他高耸的头盖骨
Look at the cranial ridge, okay?
如果恐龙狄诺是迅猛龙  他早就把摩登原始人一家吃掉了
If Dino was a velociraptor, he'd have eaten the Flintstones.
没错
Yeah. Yeah.
噢  你刚在睡午觉吗
Oh, were you taking a nap?
本来是  噢  我…
I was.  Oh, I...
请你等一下  我有插拨
Oh, wait, Tony, can you hold on? That's the other line.
喂
Hello?
是的  她在  但可以请她回电吗
Yeah, she's here, but, uh, can she call you back?
好的  谢谢
Okay, thanks.
你要回电给乔安娜
Call Joanna. Hi.
她有留电话号码吗
Did she leave a number?
你有看我抄下来吗
Did you see me write one down?
我没有她电话号码  浑蚤
I don't have her number, butt-munch.
她会再拨回来的  别这么幼稚
Well, she'll call back. Don't be such a baby.
我不幼稚  你才幼稚
I'm not a baby. You're the baby.
别烦我  那你就别来惹我
Look, you wanna get off my back? Get out of my face.
等一下  东尼  等一下…
Wait, hold on, Tony. Hold on.
你好
Hello?
Hi.
是的  没有  她人就在这里  等等
Yeah, no, she's right here. Um, hold on.
东尼  我可以晚点再打给你吗
Hi, Tony, can I call you back?
我妹的男友打来了
That's, uh... That's my sister's boyfriend.
还我啦
Give me that.
好
Okay.
亲爱的  趁我还没忘记  我的子宫帽是不是忘在你那里
Sweetie, before I forget, did I leave my diaphragm at your place?
嗨  妈
Hi, Mom.
嘿
Hey. Yeah, ha, ha.
皇宫情况如何
So, uh, how's the palace?
你居然会提到  因为我才在想…
It's funny you should mention that because I was thinking...
那些盒子是怎样
What's with the boxes?
噢  我有个消息要告诉你
Oh, uh, actually, I, uh, have some news.
乔伊会回来把他的麋鹿帽子拿走  还是要我把它扔了
Is that Joey guy gonna pick up his moose hat or should I toss it?
你何不亲自问他呢  乔伊  这位是我的新室友艾迪
Why don't you ask him yourself? This is my new roommate, Eddie.
幸会
EDDIE: Nice to meet you.
我也是
Likewise. How you doing?
这给我
Uh, I'll take that.
我就是为了这个而来的
It's, uh, what I came for, heh.
这倒是个新闻  你们怎么认识的
So this is new. Where'd you two meet?
在超级市场  在家乡味食品区
At the, uh, supermarket in the, uh, ethnic-food section.
我帮他选西班牙辣香肠  耶  哈哈哈
I helped him pick out a chorizo. Yeah. Ha-ha-ha.
是个... 我是说...   哇
It's a... I mean...  Wow.
后来我们聊了一下  他说要找地方住  而我刚好有空房间
We got to talking. And, uh, he needed a place, and I had a spare room.
这下子那是空房间了
Oh, now it's a spare room?
是啊  既然没有人在用…
Well, yeah. In that it's not being used...
我又让它空着
...and I have it to spare.
对的
Right.
好了  我拿到我来拿的东西了
Well, I, uh, got what I came for.
再见了
I'll, uh... I'll see you guys.
嘿  乔伊
Hey, Joe.
你什么时候开始在头上抹慕丝的
When'd you start using moose in your hair?
这家伙很有趣吧
Is this guy great, or what?
对啊
Yeah.
他是
Yeah, he is.
我不敢相信他找到新室友了  是谁
I can't believe he has a new roommate. Who is this guy?
艾迪什么的  他们刚认识
Uh, Eddie something. He just met him.
这关系不会持久的  他不过是  在低潮时填补空档的室友
It'll never last. He's just a rebound roommate.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
快看  快看
Ooh, check it out. Oh, check it out.
是《臭猫》的音乐录影带  天啊
It's "Smelly Cat," the video. Oh, God.
我还没看  所以要是你们不喜欢的话…
Now, okay, I haven't seen it yet, so if you don't like it...
那又如何  你们也没有人录过音乐录影带啊
...so what? None of you ever made a video.
好
Okay.
（《臭猫》 菲比·布非）
快滚出去  小猫  你好臭
Get out of here, cat! You stink!
美极了  瞧瞧我
Oh, smoking.  Oh, look at me.
臭猫  臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
他们都喂你吃什么
What are they feeding you?
臭猫  臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
这不能怪你
It's not your fault
臭臭  臭臭  真的很臭
Smelly, smelly, smelly
真的很臭的臭猫  这不能怪你
Really bad smelling smelly cat It's not your fault
臭猫  臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
天啊  我知道
Oh, my God!  I know.
我的声音真美
I sound amazing!
他们不送你去看兽医
WOMAN: They won't take you to the vet
显然你不是他们的最爱
You're obviously not their favorite pet
臭猫  臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
这不能怪你
It's not your fault
喔  不
Oh, no
我以前从没听过自己的歌声
I've never heard myself sing before.
除了在我脑袋里听到过以外
I mean, except in my own head. Oh.
这真是酷  我现在可以听到你们听到的声音了
This is so cool. Now I can hear what you hear.
相当不同  对吧
Pretty, uh, different, huh?
真是抱歉  但我真是有才华  不可思议
Oh, I am sorry, but I'm incredibly talented.
臭猫  臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
这不能怪你
It's not your fault
乔伊  怎么了
Hey, Joey. What's going on, man?
艾迪
Eddie.
早  早
Morning.  Morning.
我来拿我的邮件
I just, uh, came by to pick up my mail.
邮件在哪里  在桌上
Where's the mail?  Oh, it's, uh, over there on the table.
你现在不像以前那样  放在桌子上了吗
You don't keep it on this table anymore?
不  艾迪习惯把邮件放那边
No, Eddie likes it over there.
好吧  给你  艾迪式煎蛋
All right, here you go, my friend. Eggs à la Eddie, huh.
哦  哦
Ooh. Ooh.
太棒了
Oh, oh. That's great.
呵
Huh.
怎么了
What?
我还以为你喜欢的是我做的面包夹蛋
I thought you liked your eggs...
中间还穿个洞的那个
...with the bread with the hole in the middle, à la me.
我是啊  但艾迪的做法是这样  非常好吃
I do, but, uh, Eddie makes them this way. They're pretty darn good.
好了  大家
Well, you guys...
我走了
...I'm out of here.
再见了
See you, pals.
再见
See you.
你们两个相处得怎样   再幸福不过了
So how are you two getting along?  Oh, I couldn't be happier.
很好
Great, huh?
我为你感到高兴
I'm happy for you.
好了  我受够了
All right, that's it!
他就这样住进来  这位强尼新蛋蛋先生…
He just comes in here, Mr. Johnny New Eggs...
用他那套大摇大摆地移动我的邮件  还有那套
...with his moving the mail and his:
〝再见了  大家〞
"See you, pals."
果汁也没了
And now there's no juice!
没留果汁给想喝果汁的人  我想喝果汁
There's no juice for the people who need the juice. I need the juice!
那边还有一盒
There's another carton right over there.
这不再是关于果汁的事了  好吗
Hey, this isn't about juice anymore, all right, man?
好吧
All right.
那么是关于什么呢
So, what's it about?
蛋
Eggs.
谁的蛋蛋你比较喜欢  他的还是我的
Whose eggs do you like better, his or mine, huh?
两个人的蛋蛋我都喜欢  少来了
Well, I like both eggs equally. Oh, come on!
没有人会同样喜欢两种蛋
Nobody likes two kinds of eggs equally.
你一定比较喜欢一种胜过另一种  而我要知道答案
You like one better, and I wanna know which.
这有什么差别   你的蛋蛋现在又不在这里了
What's the difference? Your eggs aren't here anymore.
你把你的蛋蛋带走  然后搬离了这里
You took your eggs, and you left!
难道你以为我从此  就找不到新蛋蛋了吗
Did you really expect me to never find new eggs?
今晚我想要看《娱乐百分百》
I wanna watch Entertainment Tonight.
才不要  我们要看《赛伦盖提草原上的掠食者》
Tough. We're watching Predators of the Serengeti.
你们两个别争了  好吗
Ugh. Would you guys stop?
这是我的电视
It's my TV! What?
住手  咬我啊
Quit it.  Bite me!
天啊
Oh, my God.
摩妮卡一直在转台…
Well, Monica keeps changing the channel.
好  那你去跟妈妈告状啊
Aw, that's great. Why don't you tell Mommy on me?
这下子我现在变成妈咪了
Now I'm Mommy in this little play?
听着  我拒绝被卷入
Look, I refuse to get sucked into...
这一类畸型的盖勒家庭纠纷  好吗
...this weird little Geller dimension thing, okay?
所以我要去好好泡个泡泡浴…
So I'm gonna go take a nice long hot bubble bath...
因为你们两个  真的吵得我快疯了
...because you kids are driving me crazy!
我们该怎么办
What do we do about this?
把《娱乐百分百》录下来
We could tape Entertainment Tonight.
我不是说电视节目
Not that!
我是说我们
This! Us!
天啊  罗斯  你真的是…
Oh, my God, Ross, it's... You're just...
自从你来这里以后  我快被你逼疯了
Since you've been here, you're driving... Ow, ow.
摩妮卡  你又展现超音波了  好吗
Mon, you've gone ultrasonic again, all right?
我真的不能忍受
I just can't stand you being here...
你老是窝在这里
...all the time!
为什么  你为什么受不了我在这里
Why? Why can't you stand me being here?
我们相处得很愉快啊
We're just having fun.
愉快  你认为这叫愉快吗
Fun? You think this is fun?
是啊
Yeah.
我还以为我们是  像小时候那样逗着玩的
I thought we were fooling around, like when, uh... When we were kids.
罗斯  我小时候恨死你了
I hated you when we were kids.
你小时候恨死我了吗  是
You hated me when we were kids?  Yes.
我恨死你了
I hated you.
我就像〝你是我哥  所以我必须爱你〞那样爱你
I loved you in a you're-my-brother- so-I-have-to way...
但基本上我是恨你的
...but basically, I hated your guts.
你干嘛要恨我
Why did you hate me?
因为你对我很坏…
Because you were mean to me...
你老是逗我  然后很霸道
...and you teased me and you always got your way.
你不觉得那很有趣吗
That wasn't fun for you?
嗯-哼
Uh-huh.
我不敢相信你会恨我
I can't believe you hated me.
但现在我爱你啊
But now I love you.
而且不是因为我没得选择
And not just because I have to.
真的吗
Really?
耶
Yeah.
但你不能再惹火我了
You're just gonna have to stop pissing me off.
这我办得到
I can do that.
那我就不用宰掉你了
Then I won't have to kill you. Ha, ha.
那你想看《娱乐百分百》吗  想
So you wanna watch, uh, Entertainment Tonight?
谢了
Yeah, thanks.
今晚美国运动杂志
Tonight, America's premier sports magazine...
改到黄金时段播出
...moves to primetime...
你知道吗  嗯
You know what?  What?
要是你真的想看那个赛伦盖提草原什么的  也可以啦
If you really wanna watch that Serengeti thing, we can.
噢  好的
Oh, okay.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
听着  你们一定不会相信的…
Listen, you are not going to believe this...
原来录影带里  唱歌的人不是我
...but, ahem, that is not me singing on the video.
不会吧
No.
没错
Yes.
你怎么发现的
Well, how did you find out?
唱片公司寄了一张合约给我  要我签名同意…
The record company sent this paper for me to sign saying it's okay...
让别人代唱  那是我找到的第一个线索
...for someone else to sing for me. That was my first clue.
那你要怎么办呢
So, what are you gonna do?
我不能和这样的人合作
I can't work with people who would do this.
对
Sure.
这可怜的女人
I mean, this poor woman.
哪个女人
What woman?
配唱的女人
The voice woman.
她的嗓音那么好  但却没能拍录影带
She has a great voice, but she doesn't have a video.
菲比  那你怎么办
Okay, Pheebs, but what about you?
我有录影带  我讲话你们要注意听啊
I have a video. Pay attention.
这个配唱的女人  她好有才华
No, this voice woman, she's so talented.
但据制作人说
But according to the producer people...
他们说  她的样子长得不对之类的 懂吗
...they said, like, she doesn't have the right look or something. You know?
她就像那种动物收容所里的动物…
She's like one of those animals at the pound...
只因为他们不够漂亮就没有人要
...who nobody wants because they're not pretty.
或是一些老狗因为太臭又…
Or, you know, like some old dog who's kind of like stinky and...
天啊  她就是〝臭猫〞嘛
Oh, my God! She's smelly cat!
噢  这首歌真是含义深刻
Oh, oh, that song has so many levels.
嘿  艾迪
Hey, Eddie.
要玩手足球吗
You, uh, wanna play some foosball?
不要  谢了  我对运动不太有兴趣
No, thanks, man. I'm not, uh... Not really into sports.
好  没关系
Yeah, okay. All right.
没关系  看《海滩游侠》的时候到了
Doesn't matter. Time for Baywatch.
哦  啥
Oh, what?
你喜欢这部电视剧
You like that show?
你不喜欢
You don't?
哈哈  啥  不
Ha, ha, what...? No.
不过是一群漂亮女孩  在海滩上跑来跑去
I mean, it's just pretty people running around on the beach.
这就是全片的精华所在啊
Well, that's the brilliance of it.
漂亮的女孩
The pretty people.
然后跑来跑去
And the running.
我去我的房间看书吧
I'm gonna go read in my room for a little while.
好吧
Oh, oh. Okay, man.
臭猫  臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
他们都喂你吃什么
What are they feeding you?
大家一起唱
Everybody!
臭猫  臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
不是你的错
It's not your fault
摩妮卡  他们不带你去兽医院
Monica. They won't take you to the vet
钱德
Chandler.
你显然不是他们最爱的宠物
You're obviously not their favorite pet
乔伊
Joey.
你或许不是玫瑰花床   瑞秋
You may not be a bed of roses
你不是有鼻子的人的朋友
And you're no friend To those with noses
罗斯  这首歌只有这几句  抱歉了
Ross, those are the only lines we have. Sorry.
好  回到副歌
Okay. Back to the chorus.